JUDITH FETTERLEY PAPERS (APAP085) 1971-1993
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
Judith Fetterley Papers1971-1993
nam_apap085
The collection includes materials related to the women's issues with a particular emphasis on the University at Albany, SUNY. Records of particular interest are those of Albany Women Against Rape, Capital District Women, and the Caucus on Women's Rights at SUNY. Also included are issues of the publication The Spokeswoman (1971-1981).
Fetterley, Judith, 1938-
0.5
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, University at Albany, SUNY
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Biographical History
Dr. Judith Fetterley is Distinguished Teaching Professor in the Department of English at the University at Albany, SUNY. A brief description of Fetterley's research and publishing is available online at http://www.albany.edu/~jf/.
Scope and Content Information
The collection includes materials related to the women's issues with a particular emphasis on the University at Albany, SUNY. Records of particular interest are those of Albany Women Against Rape, Capital District Women, and the Caucus on Women's Rights at SUNY. Also included are issues of the publication The Spokeswoman (1971-1981).
Related collections include Andrea Lurie (APAP-051), Joan Schultz (APAP-216), Gloria DeSole (APAP-215), and the Caucus on Women's Rights at SUNY, Albany Chapter (UA-089). Additional related collections can be found at the subject page for Women and Education.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection has no series.
Subject and Genre Headings
Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Albany, New York; Education; Albany, New York; Women; Education; Albany, New York; Albany, New York; Fetterley, Judith, 1938-; State University of New York at Albany; Women’s rights--New York (State); Women--Employment--New York (State); Universities and colleges--New York (State)--Faculty
Container List
- Albany Women Against Rape, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Capital District Women, ca. 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Challenge: Women in Higher Education, Summer Institutes, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Course, English 590: Women in Literature, Syllabi, Exams, etc., 1976-1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Violence Against Women, University at Albany, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- "Women and Tenure at Albany: A Guide for Faculty," Women's Concerns Committee, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Spokeswoman volume 1, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Spokeswoman volume 2, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- The Spokeswoman volume 3, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- The Spokeswoman volume 4, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- The Spokeswoman volume 5, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- The Spokeswoman volume 6, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- The Spokeswoman volume 7, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- The Spokeswoman volume 8, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- The Spokeswoman volume 9, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- The Spokeswoman volume 10, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- The Spokeswoman volume 11, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)